YMCA ARMED SERVICES DEPARTMENT:
University of Minnesota Libraries
- Club Histories
  - Army-Navy Clubs:
    - Hempstead, NY, 1941-1946.; 6 folders. (Box 56)
    - Hempstead, NY, 1941-1946.; 2 folders. (Box 57)
    - New York, NY, 1945. (Box 57)
    - Newburgh, NY, 1944-1946.; 2 folders. (Box 80)
    - Nyack, NY, 1943-1946.; 3 folders. (Box 80)
    - Oswego, NY, 1942-1946.; 3 folders. (Box 80)
    - Rome, NY, 1943. (Box 57)
    - Watertown, NY, 1941-1947.; 4 folders. (Box 57)
    - Osborn, OH, 1942-1946. (Box 81)
    - Enid, OK, 1943-1946. (Box 57)
    - Lawton, OK, 1944-1950.; 2 folders. (Box 58)
    - Lawton, OK (African American), 1945-1950.; 4 folders. (Box 58)
    - McAlester, OK (African American), 1943-1946. (Box 58)
    - Muskogee, OK, 1942-1945.; 3 folders. (Box 81)
    - Norman, OK, 1944-1946. (Box 81)
    - Oklahoma City, OK, 1943-1946.; 3 folders. (Box 81)
    - Woodward, OK, 1943-1945. (Box 58)
    - Astoria, OR, 1947-1956. (Box 58)
    - Medford, OR, 1942-1946. (Box 58)
    - Pendleton, OR, 1941-1945.; 2 folders. (Box 81)
    - Portland, OR, 1942-1943. (Box 59)
    - Salem, OR, 1942-1945. (Box 59)
    - Chester, PA, 1946. (Box 59)
    - Farrell, PA (African American), 1943-1946. (Box 59)
    - Greenville, PA, 1943-1945. (Box 59)
    - Harrisburg, PA, 1941-1946.; 3 folders. (Box 59)
    - Harrisburg, PA (African American), 1944-1946. (Box 59)
    - Lebanon, PA, 1941-1946.; 2 folders. (Box 59)
    - Lebanon, PA, 1941-1946. (Box 60)
    - Middletown, PA, 1941-1945. (Box 60)
    - Sharon, PA, 1943-1945. (Box 60)
    - Tobyhanna, PA, 1945. (Box 60)
    - San Juan, Puerto Rico, 1948-1949. (Box 60)
    - Davisville, RI, 1946. (Box 60)
    - Jamestown, RI, 1942-1946. (Box 60)
    - Newport, RI (African American), 1912, 1944-1950.; 2 folders. (Box 60)
    - Beaufort, SC, 1942-1947.; 3 folders. (Box 60)
    - Beaufort, NC (African American), 1944-1946. (Box 61)
    - Charleston, SC, 1942-1947.; 3 folders. (Box 61)
    - Charleston, SC (African American), 1942-1945. (Box 61)
    - Columbia, SC, 1942-1947.; 2 folders. (Box 61)
    - Congaree, SC, 1943-1945. (Box 61)
    - North Charleston, SC, 1942-1946. (Box 81)
    - North Charleston, SC, 1943-1946.; 2 folders. (Box 82)
    - Spartanburg, SC, 1942-1946.; 2 folders. (Box 61)
    - Spartanburg, SC (African American), 1942-1945. (Box 61)
    - Sumter, SC, 1942-1949. (Box 62)
    - Walterboro, SC, 1942-1945. (Box 62)
    - Walterboro, SC (African American), 1943-1945. (Box 62)
    - Rapid City, SD, 1949-1950. (Box 62)
    - Sioux Falls, SD, 1942-1946.; 2 folders. (Box 62)
    - Sioux Falls, SD (African American), 1944-1945. (Box 62)
    - Clarksville, TN, 1943-1947. (Box 62)
    - Dyersburg, TN, 1942-1945. (Box 62)
    - Dyersburg, TN (African American), 1943-1945. (Box 62)
    - McKenzie, TN, 1942-1945. (Box 62)
    - Memphis, TN, 1942-1945. (Box 62)
    - Paris, TN, 1941-1945.; 2 folders. (Box 82)
    - Tullohoma, TN, 1941-1944. (Box 63)
    - Tullohoma, TN (African American), 1941-1945. (Box 63)
    - Big Springs, TX, 1943-1945. (Box 63)
    - Brackettville, TX, 1942-1946. (Box 63)
    - Brownsville, TX, 1940-1946. (Box 63)
    - Brownwood, TX, 1941-1946.; 2 folders. (Box 63)
    - Brownwood, TX (African American), 1941-1945. (Box 63)
    - Bryan, TX, 1943-1945. (Box 63)
    - Childress, TX, 1942-1946.; 2 folders. (Box 64)
    - Corpus Christi, TX, 1941-1947.; 5 folders. (Box 64)
    - Dallas, TX, 1943-1945. (Box 64)
    - Del Rio, TX, 1943-1945. (Box 64)
    - Denton, TX, 1943-1946. (Box 65)
    - Gainesville, TX, 1943-1946. (Box 65)
    - Galveston, TX, 1941-1946.; 3 folders. (Box 65)
    - Gatesville, TX, 1942-1946.; 2 folders. (Box 65)
    - Gatesville, TX (African American), 1943-1945. (Box 65)
    - Houston, TX, 1942-1946.; 2 folders. (Box 65)
    - Houston, TX (African American), 1943-1946. (Box 65)
    - Kingsville, TX, 1942-1946. (Box 66)
    - Kingsville, TX (African American), 1945-1946. (Box 66)
    - Marfa, TX (African American), 1943-1944. (Box 66)
    - Mineral Wells, TX, 1942-1946.; 3 folders. (Box 66)
    - Mineral Wells, TX (African American), 1941-1943. (Box 66)
    - Orange, TX, 1942-1947.; 2 folders. (Box 82)
    - Paris, TX, 1941-1946.; 5 folders. (Box 82)
    - Port Lavaca, TX, 1943-1944. (Box 66)
    - San Angelo, TX (African American), 1943-1946. (Box 66)
    - San Angelo, TX, 1942-1946.; 2 folders. (Box 66)
    - South San Antonio, TX, 1942-1946. (Box 67)
    - Temple, TX, 1942-1947.; 4 folders. (Box 67)
    - Temple, TX (African American), 1943-1946. (Box 67)
    - Tyler, TX, 1943-1945. (Box 67)
    - Waco, TX, 1942-1946. (Box 67)
    - Waco, TX (African American), 1945-1946. (Box 67)
    - Wichita Falls, TX, 1943-1947.; 3 folders. (Box 68)
    - Wichita Falls, TX (African American), 1943-1946. (Box 68)
    - Murray, UT, 1942-1944. (Box 83)
    - Blackstone, VA, 1943-1945.; 3 folders. (Box 68)
    - Blackstone, VA (African American), 1942-1945.; 2 folders. (Box 68)
    - Bowling Green, VA, 1942-1947. (Box 69)
    - Bowling Green, VA (African American), 1943-1945. (Box 69)
    - Crewe, VA, 1942-1946. (Box 69)
    - Fort Myer, VA, 1945. (Box 69)
    - Fredericksburg, VA, 1941-1946. (Box 69)
    - Hampton, VA, 1942-1947.; 2 folders. (Box 69)
    - Hopewell, VA, 1941-1947.; 2 folders. (Box 69)
    - Lackey, VA (African American), 1945-1947. (Box 69)
    - Langley Field, VA, 1941-1945. (Box 69)
    - Newport News, VA (African American), 1944-1947. (Box 70)
    - Norfolk, VA, 1941-1947.; 5 folders. (Box 70)
    - Norfolk, VA, 1941-1947.; 3 folders. (Box 83)
    - Norfolk, VA (African American), 1942-1947. (Box 70)
    - Petersburg, VA, 1942-1947.; 7 folders. (Box 83)
    - Petersburg, VA, 1942-1947.; 2 folders. (Box 84)
    - Portsmouth, VA, 1932-1953.; 3 folders. (Box 70)
    - Richmond, VA, 1943-1947.; 6 folders. (Box 71)
    - Richmond, VA (African American), 1943-1947. (Box 71)
    - Sandston, VA, 1942-1946. (Box 71)
    - Warrenton, VA, 1943-1947.; 3 folders. (Box 72)
    - Williamsburg, VA, 1943-1946.; 2 folders. (Box 72)
    - Williamsburg, VA (African American), 1944-1947. (Box 72)
    - Yorktown, VA, 1942-1947.; 2 folders. (Box 72)
    - Burlington, VT, 1941-1944. (Box 72)
    - Ephrata, WA, 1943-1945. (Box 72)
    - Moses Lake, WA, 1943-1946. (Box 84)
    - Pasco, WA, 1941-1947.; 2 folders. (Box 84)
    - Port Angeles, WA, 1942-1946. (Box 73)
    - Port Townsend, WA, 1941-1953.; 3 folders. (Box 73)
    - Seattle, WA (African American), 1944-1946.; 2 folders. (Box 73)
    - Tacoma, WA, 1941-1946.; 3 folders. (Box 73)
    - Tacoma, WA, 1941-1946.; 2 folders. (Box 74)
    - Walla Walla, WA, 1942-1945. (Box 74)
    - Walla Walla, WA (African American), 1944-1945. (Box 74)
    - Madison, WI, 1942-1946.; 2 folders. (Box 74)
    - Madison, WI (African American), 1943-1945. (Box 74)
    - Tomah, WI, 1942-1946. (Box 74)
    - Cheyenne, WY, 1941-1946. (Box 74)
    - Cheyenne, WY, 1941-1946.; 4 folders. (Box 75)
  - Photographs:
    Includes photographs removed from the club histories, arranged by state and city.
    - Alabama - California., 79 folders. (Box 125 (A-V))
    - Colorado - Georgia., 60 folders. (Box 126 (A-V))
    - Idaho - Louisiana., 68 folders. (Box 127 (A-V))
    - Mississippi - Ohio., 83 folders. (Box 128 (A-V))
    - Oklahoma - Utah., 97 folders. (Box 129 (A-V))
    - Virginia - Wyoming., 68 folders. (Box 130 (A-V))
- Administrative Files
  - General Files:
    - Accounting, 1942-1949, 1964-1971.; 2 folders. (Box 85)
    - Accounting procedures, 1942-1943, 1958-1975; 4 folders. (Box 85)
    - Adolescent girls, 1943, 1945. (Box 85)
    - Administration procedures, 1960-1967. (Box 85)
    - Administrative staff conference, 1968-1972. (Box 85)
    - Agencies, 1949. (Box 85)
    - Agreements, 1941-1955.; 2 folders. (Box 85)
    - Agreements/charter, 1950-1951.; 3 folders. (Box 85)
    - Agreement with agencies, 1941-1942. (Box 85)
    - Agreement concerning agencies' buildings, 1942. (Box 85)
    - Agreement concerning Building Bureau, 1944. (Box 85)
    - Agreement with Community War Services, 1941-1943. (Box 85)
    - Agreements-corporate data charter, 1955-1964.; 2 folders. (Box 85)
    - Agreement with Federal Security Agency, 1941-1945.; 2 folders. (Box 85)
    - Agreement with USO foreign subsidiaries, 1943. (Box 85)
    - Agreement with ODHWS, 1942. (Box 85)
    - Agreements, YMCA-USO overseas buildings, 1942-1948.; 3 folders. (Box 85)
    - Agreements with senior and junior agencies, 1942. (Box 85)
    - Agreement concerning termination of operations, 1944. (Box 85)
    - Agreement with War Department, 1942. (Box 85)
    - Agreement with Red Cross, undated. (Box 85)
    - Alien employees, 1943. (Box 85)
    - Anderson, Sam, 1967, 1970-1973 (Box 120)
    - Anniversary materials, 1950.; 3 folders. (Box 85)
    - Anniversary materials, 20th, 1961. (Box 85)
    - Anniversary materials, 25th, 1965.; 4 folders. (Box 85)
    - Anniversary materials, 30th, 1971.; 2 folders. (Box 85)
    - Annual meetings, 1941-1947., 2 folders. (Box 85)
    - Annual reports, 1942-1948, 1951-1961.; 3 folders. (Box 85)
    - Annual reports, 1962-1975.; 5 folders. (Box 86)
    - Approvals, 1942. (Box 86)
    - Army Service Forces directive, 1944. (Box 86)
    - Associated Services for the Armed Forces (ASAF), 1949-1951.; 2 folders. (Box 86)
    - ASAF, agency executives, minutes, 1950-1951. (Box 86)
    - ASAF, agency funds expended, 1950, 1976.; 2 folders. (Box 86)
    - ASAF, budget and finance, 1950-1951.; 2 folders. (Box 86)
    - ASAF, circular letters and memos, 1950. (Box 86)
    - USO and ASAF consolidation plan, 1951. (Box 86)
    - ASAF operations policies, 1950-1951. (Box 86)
    - ASAF local committees, 1950-1951. (Box 86)
    - ASAF, merger, 1950-1951.; 3 folders. (Box 86)
    - ASAF, papers, 1950. (Box 86)
    - ASAF, starter kit, 1950. (Box 86)
    - ASAF withdrawal from United Defense Fund, 1955.; 2 folders. (Box 86)
    - Athletic contests, basketball, 1948-1955. (Box 86)
    - Athletic contests, bowling, 1945-1955. (Box 86)
    - Audits, 1942-1947. (Box 86)
    - Audits and requirements of local United Way, 1974-1977. (Box 86)
    - Automobiles, 1941-1946. (Box 86)
    - Autonomous councils questionnaire, 1965. (Box 86)
    - Awards, 1970-1974. (Box 86)
    - Background information, 1950, 1974-1976. (Box 86)
    - Bank accounts, states, 1942-1946.; 10 folders. (Box 118)
    - Beer and liquor policy, 1941-1942. (Box 86)
    - Birthday-anniversaries, 1942-1943. (Box 86)
    - Blue Ribbon study, 1975.; 2 folders. (Box 86)
    - Bock, Peter, 1975-1976. (Box 86)
    - Budget, 1941. (Box 86)
    - Budget, 1941.; 2 folders. (Box 87)
    - Budgets, 1941-1942. (Box 87)
    - Budget, 1942-1943.; 6 folders. (Box 87)
    - Budget, 1944-1946, 1951-1952; 2 folders. (Box 87)
    - Budget, 1975-1976.; 4 folders. (Box 87)
    - Budget, Armed Services financing, 1950. (Box 87)
    - Budgets, centers, 1975-1976. (Box 87)
    - Budget and finance, 1953-1954, 1965-1974.; 6 folders. (Box 87)
    - Budget changes, 1975-1976.; 2 folders. (Box 87)
    - Budget, national, 1973-1976. (Box 87)
    - Budgets, publications, 1961, 1963-1964. (Box 118)
    - Building attendance graphs, 1948-1958. (Box 87)
    - Building facilities, local clubs, 1942-1944. (Box 87)
    - Buildings, maintenance policy, 1951-1960. (Box 87)
    - Building services, 1968-1973. (Box 87)
    - Campaign, 1963-1971.; 2 folders. (Box 87)
    - Campaign, 1941.; 3 folders. (Box 88)
    - Campaign assignments, 1958-1960. (Box 88)
    - Campaign kit, 1966-1972. (Box 88)
    - Campaign promotion, 1975. (Box 88)
    - Campaign quotas, 1972. (Box 88)
    - Campaign report, 1971-1973. (Box 88)
    - Carl, Fred, files, 1975.; 2 folders. (Box 88)
    - Centers, expense, 1976.; 2 folders. (Box 88)
    - Central Atlantic Area, 1941-1942. (Box 120)
    - Central Atlantic Area, 1937-1943. (Box 118)
    - Certificate of incorporation, constitution, by-laws, 1941-1943.; 3 folders. (Box 88)
    - Changeover, 1963-1977.; 2 folders. (Box 88)
    - Chase investments, 1973-1976. (Box 88)
    - Church/YMCA relations, 1942-1951.; 6 folders. (Box 88)
    - City histories, outline, 1944. (Box 88)
    - Clippings, 1940-1947.; 3 folders. (Box 88)
    - Closing instructions for a USO club, 1950. (Box 88)
    - Committee reports, 1962-1974. (Box 88)
    - Community conducted operations, 1943-1944. (Box 88)
    - Community grants-in-aid, 1942-1944. (Box 88)
    - Community Managed USO Operations and Volunteer Relationships, 1943. (Box 88)
    - Community social problems study, 1941-1944. (Box 88)
    - Consultative services, 1967-1969. (Box 88)
    - Contingent liabilities, 1973. (Box 88)
    - Contingent liabilities (termination reserve), 1953-1967.; 2 folders. (Box 89)
    - Conferences, staff, 1941-1946.; 4 folders. (Box 89)
    - Congressional charter request, 1976. (Box 89)
    - Conscientious objectors, 1943-1944, 1966.; 2 folders. (Box 89)
    - Constitution, by-laws and articles of incorporation, 1941-1943.; 2 folders. (Box 89)
    - Comptrollers conferences, 1943-1948.; 2 folders. (Box 89)
    - Corporate involvement, undated. (Box 118)
    - Corporate planning, 1975. (Box 89)
    - Correspondence regarding literature, undated. (Box 89)
    - Correspondence and reports regarding organization of USO, 1940-1941.; 5 folders. (Box 89)
    - Councils, undated, 1942-1943, 1946, 1949.; 3 folders. (Box 89)
    - Council of Japan, 1971-1973.; 2 folders. (Box 89)
    - Council of New England annual meeting, 1975. (Box 118)
    - Counseling service, 1945. (Box 89)
    - Creed for workers, undated. (Box 89)
    - Davison, General Michael S., 1975-1976. (Box 89)
    - Defense Morale Conference, proceedings, 1941. (Box 89)
    - Department of Defense, agreements, 1951-1960. (Box 89)
    - Department of Defense, survey, 1974-1975. (Box 89)
    - Directories, 1941-1944, 1946, 1948-1950; 10 folders. (Box 89)
    - Directory of USO operations, 1944-1945, 1964, 1975-1976.; 5 folders. (Box 90)
    - Directories, 1942-1945.; 4 folders. (Box 120)
    - Directories of YMCA/USO services, 1944-1945. (Box 90)
    - Distribution of Yank, 1943. (Box 90)
    - Drug education, circa 1970. (Box 90)
    - Elimination of designations, 1942-1947.; 4 folders. (Box 90)
    - Emergency job program, 1975. (Box 90)
    - Endowment program, 1970-1972. (Box 90)
    - Endorsements, 1942. (Box 90)
    - Ex-servicemen, 1944. (Box 90)
    - Expense computerized, 1974-1976. (Box 90)
    - Expenses, National Board, 1941-1942. (Box 90)
    - Field service manual, 1943. (Box 90)
    - Field services, general, 1948-1959. (Box 118)
    - Field supervision, 1945. (Box 90)
    - Files and records, undated. (Box 90)
    - Films, 1952-1963.; 3 folders. (Box 118)
    - Financial policies and procedures manual, 1943. (Box 90)
    - Financial statements, 1941, 1949, 1973-1976.; 3 folders. (Box 90)
    - Five year report, volunteer services, 1941-1946. (Box 90)
    - Flags, 1941. (Box 90)
    - Foreign, miscellaneous, undated. (Box 90)
    - Forms, undated.; 2 folders. (Box 90)
    - Future service to the Armed Forces, papers, 1945-1950. (Box 90)
    - Furnishings, lists, 1941. (Box 90)
    - Girls Service Organization (GSO), 1942-1946.; 3 folders. (Box 90)
    - General folders, 1940s-1970s.; 5 folders. (Box 90)
    - General folders, 1940s-1970s.; 12 folders. (Box 91)
      General files may contain duplicate material found in other folders.
    - General correspondence, 1970-1971.; 2 folders. (Box 91)
    - Gold Plate Dinner, Tokyo, 1971. (Box 120)
    - Handbooks, 1941.; 2 folders. (Box 91)
    - Handbook for volunteers, 1967. (Box 118)
    - Historical record disposition, 1944. (Box 120)
    - History project, 1943-1948, 1980. (Box 91)
    - Hostesses, 1943. (Box 91)
    - "Hot Line to Home", 1970. (Box 91)
    - Housing projects, 1946. (Box 91)
    - Imprest funds, expenses, 1974-1975. (Box 91)
    - Industrial service, 1941-1946.; 9 folders. (Box 91)
    - Industrial service, annual reports, 1942-1945. (Box 91)
    - Industrial service, monthly summary, 1944, 1946.; 2 folders. (Box 91)
    - Industrial USO, Dayton, OH clippings, 1929. (Box 91)
    - Industrial USO, Glenn Roberts Reports, 1944-1946.; 2 folders. (Box 91)
    - Industrial USO, local reports, 1944-1945. (Box 91)
    - Industrial USO, miscellaneous, 1941-1945.; 2 folders. (Box 91)
    - Industrial USO, monthly summaries, 1944-1945.; 4 folders. (Box 92)
    - Industrial USO, reports, industrial service, 1942-1946.; 3 folders. (Box 92)
    - Industrial folder, reports and special studies, 1945-1946. (Box 92)
    - Industrial USO, staff conferences, 1941-1945.; 3 folders. (Box 92)
    - Industrial YMCA statistics, 1945. (Box 92)
    - Industrial YMCA summaries, 1941-1944.; 6 folders. (Box 92)
    - Industrial service, units of operation and personnel, 1942-1946. (Box 92)
    - Institute, workshops, 1944-1945. (Box 92)
    - Insurance, 1944-1946, 1948-1950, 1964-1976.; 3 folders. (Box 92)
    - Inter-agency orientation course, 1944. (Box 92)
    - Interview information, 1969. (Box 92)
    - Inventories, 1949, 1976.; 2 folders. (Box 92)
    - Inventories, 1971-1975.; 5 folders. (Box 118)
    - Job analysis, 1943-1944. (Box 92)
    - Joint agency operation plan, 1944. (Box 92)
    - Joint occupancy, 1941-1945.; 3 folders. (Box 92)
    - Junior volunteers, 1974-1977. (Box 118)
    - Kalk, Lieutenant Stanton, fund, 1954-1956. (Box 92)
    - Labor unions, 1943. (Box 92)
    - LeMar versus Commonwealth of Virginia, 1944-1946.; 2 folders. (Box 92)
    - Leases, 1941-1942. (Box 92)
    - Leases, 1941-1946.; 3 folders. (Box 93)
    - Letter writing etiquette, undated. (Box 118)
    - Library lists, 1941. (Box 93)
    - List of representatives of 6 USO organizations, 1941. (Box 93)
    - Literature distributed to clubs, list, 1943-1946. (Box 118)
    - Little, Arthur D., Inc., report, 1974-1975. (Box 93)
    - Local bulletins, 1941. (Box 93)
    - Locations, 1942. (Box 93)
    - Mail, 1976. (Box 93)
    - Maintenance manual, 1952. (Box 120)
    - Maneuvers, 1943-1944. (Box 93)
    - Manual, clubhouse dedication, undated. (Box 93)
    - Manual on community conducted operations, 1943. (Box 93)
    - Manual, maintenance, undated. (Box 93)
    - Manual for work in War Production areas, undated. (Box 118)
    - Map revision, 1966-1967. (Box 93)
    - March music, 1942. (Box 93)
    - Meeting, ad hoc group, 1977. (Box 93)
    - Menster, Mike, 1973-1976. (Box 93)
    - Merchant Marine, 1942. (Box 93)
    - Military hospitals, 1945-1946. (Box 93)
    - Military installations, 1949-1960.; 6 folders. (Box 93)
    - Military Personnel and their Families and Central Maryland Community Services: New Directions, 1974. (Box 93)
    - Miscellaneous USO, 1940s. (Box 93)
    - Mobile service, 1942-1943. (Box 93)
    - Monthly statistical report instructions, 1941-1945. (Box 93)
    - Monthly summary worksheets, 1943, 1945-1946.; 6 folders. (Box 93)
    - Morrill, Justin, 1970-1974. (Box 93)
    - Musical extravaganza, Corpus Christi Naval air station, 1975. (Box 93)
    - National board professional staff changes, 1974-1975. (Box 93)
    - National book campaign, 1941. (Box 93)
    - National Council, 1944-1945.; 2 folders. (Box 93)
    - National Golf Day, 1952-1954. (Box 93)
    - National Photography Contest, 1942. (Box 93)
    - National staff information, 1977. (Box 93)
    - National USO survey implementation plan, 1963. (Box 93)
    - National volunteer awards, 1974. (Box 93)
    - National War Fund, 1943-1944. (Box 93)
    - Navy Y programs, 1944. (Box 93)
    - Needs of U.S. Armed Services personnel, report, 1975. (Box 93)
    - Negotiations, USO/YMCA, 1962-1977. (Box 93)
    - USO New England, 1970-1973. (Box 118)
    - The New USO, speech given by Harvey Firestone, Jr., 1949. (Box 118)
    - North Central Area, 1941-1942. (Box 120)
    - Notebook, 1961-1963.; 2 folders. (Box 93)
    - Operations handbook, 1969. (Box 94)
    - Operational method, 1973. (Box 94)
    - Operations, Department of, 1942. (Box 94)
    - Operations, USO information survey, 1957. (Box 94)
    - Organizational chart, undated. (Box 94)
    - Organizational material, 1941-1942. (Box 120)
    - Organization and management study, 1970. (Box 94)
    - Overseas operations, 1956-1958. (Box 120)
    - Overseas operations, 1972-1976. (Box 94)
    - Overseas payroll, 1969-1974. (Box 94)
    - Overseas staff housing, 1965. (Box 94)
    - Pacific Southwest area, 1941. (Box 120)
    - Pearl Harbor 25th anniversary, 1966. (Box 94)
    - Personnel, 1959-1972, 1974-1976.; 3 folders. (Box 94)
    - Personnel, confidential information on local directors salaries, etc., 1943-1946.; 2 folders. (Box 94)
    - Personnel evaluation, 1973. (Box 120)
    - Personnel policy, local councils, 1963-1964. (Box 120)
    - Personnel practices, 1941-1942. (Box 120)
    - Personnel practice manual, 1944. (Box 94)
    - Personnel reference sheet, 1968. (Box 120)
    - Photographs, undated. (Box 94)
    - Plan book, 1950. (Box 94)
    - Policies, 1963-1970. (Box 94)
    - Policies, administration, general, 1960-1962. (Box 94)
    - Policies, general, 1960-1972. (Box 94)
    - Policies, general, administrative directive #9, 1967-1969. (Box 94)
    - Policies, miscellaneous, undated, 1943-1946.; 4 folders. (Box 94)
    - Post-USO services, 1947. (Box 118)
    - Post-USO services, 1947.; 2 folders. (Box 119)
    - Post-USO services, 1947.; 2 folders. (Box 120)
    - Pre-induction training, 1956-1960.; 3 folders. (Box 94)
    - Presentation materials for National Council, 1952. (Box 120)
    - President's report, 1948. (Box 94)
    - Procedures for establishing and maintaining physical properties of USO, 1950-1964.; 2 folders. (Box 94)
    - Profile, 1973-1976. (Box 94)
    - Programs, 1950-1977.; 2 folders. (Box 120)
    - Program bulletin, 1941-1947.; 7 folders. (Box 94)
    - Program bulletin, 1948-1954, undated.; 10 folders. (Box 95)
    - Program division, Overseas Flier, 1943-1945.; 2 folders. (Box 95)
    - Program Exchange, correspondence, 1961-1967. (Box 95)
    - Program manual, 1967-1968.; 3 folders. (Box 95)
    - Program for Pre-induction education, 1950s. (Box 95)
    - Program by pros, 1967-1973.; 5 folders. (Box 95)
    - Program, Servicemen's Council, undated. (Box 95)
    - Program statistics, 1946. (Box 95)
    - Program suggestions, 1943-1944, 1947.; 2 folders. (Box 120)
    - Programming, undated. (Box 120)
    - Programs, 1950-1976.; 2 folders. (Box 120)
    - Programs, Christmas, undated. (Box 95)
    - Programs, trivia, undated. (Box 95)
    - Public affairs education workbook, 1944. (Box 95)
    - Public relations, 1971, 1974.; 2 folders. (Box 95)
    - Public relations, Christmas gift program, 1974. (Box 95)
    - Public relations, general, 1967-1972.; 2 folders. (Box 95)
    - Public relations, materials, 1959-1960.; 2 folders. (Box 95)
    - Public relations program, 1954-1955. (Box 95)
    - Public relations, Vietnam service to Armed Forces, 1965-1972.; 2 folders. (Box 95)
    - Publicity, public relations, 1962-1967. (Box 95)
    - Publicity, public relations, 1962-1967. (Box 96)
    - Publicity, USO in Action, 1955-1959. (Box 96)
    - The Races of Mankind, 1943-1944.; 2 folders. (Box 96)
    - Reactivation, 1947-1951.; 3 folders. (Box 96)
    - Recognition, 1950-1960. (Box 96)
    - Recreation centers, 1941. (Box 96)
    - Region 8, 1968-1971. (Box 120)
    - Regional staff conference, 1967.; 3 folders. (Box 96)
    - Religious work, 1945-1947.; 2 folders. (Box 96)
    - Reorganization/charter, 1941, 1949-1950. (Box 96)
    - Reorganization, 1948.; 3 folders. (Box 96)
    - Reorganization study, 1963. (Box 96)
    - Report, 1943. (Box 120)
    - Report of Executive Director, 1963. (Box 120)
    - Report of the National staff development conference, 1956. (Box 96)
    - Reports, preliminary, 1974. (Box 96)
    - Returning servicemen and women, 1943-1944. (Box 96)
    - Role of agencies, 1976-1977. (Box 96)
    - Rymer files, 1942-1945, 1963.; 3 folders. (Box 96)